Guide to the Raymond Germann Photograph Collection 1978-2016 PR 311
New-York Historical Society
- [255] Signs in window, Catherine Street, Chinatown, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
- [256] Slaughtered Lamb Pub, West 4th Street, Greenwich Village, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
- [257] Heifer's Saloon, Washington Street, Chelsea, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
- [258] Joseph's Shoe Store sign, West 181st Street, Washington Heights, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
- [259] Mannequin, Stuyvesant Park, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
- [260] Hand on building, West 42nd Street near 8th Avenue, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
- [261] Signs, multi services, West 180th Street near Broadway, Washington Heights, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
- [262] Courtyard with chess board, East 48th Street and 3rd Avenue, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
- [263] Triangle road markings, Greenwich Avenue looking north from Christopher Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
- [264] Blarney Stone Bar, 3rd Avenue and East 44th Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
- [265] 88 Piano Festival, Lincoln Center, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
- [266] Mural painting, the High Line, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
- [267] 5 Pointz Building, color print #1, Jackson Avenue, Long Island City, Queens, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
- [268] 5 Pointz Building, color print #2, Jackson Avenue, Long Island City, Queens, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
- [269] Taxi Parts shop, 10th Avenue around West 37th Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
- [270] Pier 17, looking northwest, South Street Seaport, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
- [271] Tribute to Trayvon Martin, Broadway, Chelsea, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
- [272] Naked Cowgirl, Times Square, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
- [273] Wynton Marsalis poster, Jazz at Lincoln Center, Broadway, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
- [274] Staff worker in park, Washington Square, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
- [275] Women's slacks apparel store, St. Nicholas Avenue and West 176th Street, Washington Heights, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
- [276] JDS Used Tires, Amsterdam Avenue and West 173rd Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
- [277] Window with four female figures, Orchard Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
- [278] A. N. Headwear, Orchard Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
- [279] Heavenly Body Works graffiti, West 22nd Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
- [280] Tiger's Head in window, Orchard Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
- [281] NY Taxi, East Side, Madison Avenue, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
- [282] Parking garage, Brooklyn, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
- [283] Eyes in fence, Times Square, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
- [284] Turn To Me Lettering, Brooklyn, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
- [285] Mulberia Furniture Store, St. Nicholas Avenue and West 177th Street, Washington Heights, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
- [286] Maleta Clothing Store, West 181st Street, Washington Heights, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
- [287] The Gowanus Canal, Brooklyn, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
- [288] Man having conversation holding sculpture, West 24th Street, Chelsea, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
- [289] Sheep at service station art installation, Tenth Avenue, Chelsea, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
- [290] My Way Coffee Shop, West 23rd Street at Broadway, Chelsea, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
- [291] Sailing School, Battery Park, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
- [292] Man with feather in hat, 6th Avenue, Midtown, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
- [293] Musician and sombrero, Washington Square, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
- [294] Clothing store with suspended mannequins, West 181st Street, Washington Heights, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
- [295] Dalai Lama photo on bus, 7th Avenue, Midtown, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
- [296] Bicycle and fatality sign, West 23rd Street near Broadway, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
- [297] Man on telephone with sign, 6th Avenue, Midtown, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
- [298] Street fair with male mannequin, 6th Avenue, Greenwich Village, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
- [299] Downtown Tire Shop, 10th Avenue at West 37th Street, 2013 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
- [300] Aeropostale signs, Times Square, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
- [301] Elevated tracks with shadows, Broadway and 238th Street, Bronx, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
- [302] Car doors/city vehicles on wall, Wythe Street, Williamsburg, Brooklyn. Color print, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
- [303] Pig on window, restaurant, West 13th Street near 9th Avenue, Greenwich Village, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
- [304] Corridor leading to PATH trains, near Chambers Street, Lower Manhattan, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
- [305] Tello's Restaurant, 8th Avenue at West 19th Street, Chelsea, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
- [306] Fulton Streeet Subway Station, Lower Manhattan, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
- [307] Express sign, Times Square, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
- [308] Car doors on side of building, Wythe Street, Williamsburg, Brooklyn, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
- [309] Prayer Station, Park Row, near the Brooklyn Bridge, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
- [310] Long Island Rail Road West Side Yard, 12th Avenue at 34th Street, from the High Line, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
- [311] Williamsburg Bridge from Kent Avenue, Williamsburg, Brooklyn, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
- [312] Jennifer's Cafe, 1st Avenue at 4th Street, Manhattan, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
- [313] Store with signs, Pike and Division Street, Chinatown, 2015 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
- [314] Sephora store, Times Square, Broadway, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
- [315] Bus Station with schedule signs displayed, Division Street, Chinatown, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
- [316] Signs on side of building in Chinese, with numbers, Forsythe Street, Chinatown, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
- [317] Outdoor dining area with umbrellas, Battery Park, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
- [318] Aurora Truck, street fair, 8th Avenue, Midtown, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
- [319] Building entrance with sculpture on the wall, West 50th Street near Broadway, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
- [320] Building with posters in windows, Lafayette Street, Soho, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
- [321] Heineken sign, Chrystie and Rivington Streets, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
- [322] Dental office, Fulton Street, Brooklyn, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
- [323] Bus stop, South Ferry, Lower Manhattan, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
- [324] Mural on wall, Houston Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
- [325] Shoe Zone store, Fulton Street, Brooklyn, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
- [326] Tiffany's retail store, East 57th Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
- [327] Mister Softee ice cream man and truck, Broadway, Midtown, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
- [328] Mural ad, 5th Avenue, Midtown, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
- [329] Lobby, One World Trade Center [Freedom Tower], Vesey Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
- [330] Hudson River, New York Harbor, looking toward NJ, near Christopher Street, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
- [331] Violins on building, Canal Street near West Side Highway. Color print., 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
- [332] Police protest posters, 125th Street, Harlem, 2015 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
- [333] Food Truck with woman, South Street Seaport, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
- [334] Mannequins with man on telephone, Canal Street, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
- [335] Teitel's Italian grocery store, Arthur Avenue, the Bronx, 2015 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
- [336] Parking lot with figures on side of building, Lafayette Street, Soho, 2015 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
- [337] Minskoff Theater lobby, West 45th Street and Broadway, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
- [338] The New School, 5th Avenue and 14th Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
- [339] Girl in window advertisement, 5th Avenue, midtown, 2014 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
- [361] Taco Stand, South Street, South Streeet Seaport, NYC, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
- [362] Highbridge looking South from East River around West 172nd Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
- [363] Ironworks building, West 25th Street at 10th Avenue, n.d. (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
- [364] Poster with ladies, Fulton Street, Brooklyn, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
- [365] Building with insect drawings, Thompson and Grand Streets, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
- [366] Roosevelt Ave. Subway entrance #1, Jackson Heights, Queens, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
- [367] Roosevelt Ave. Subway entrance #2, Jackson Heights, Queens, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
- [368] Path Train Sculpture, street view, near Vesey Street, 2016 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
- [369] George Washington Bridge Bus Terminal, Broadway and West 178th Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
- [370] Number 7 Subway station at 11th Avenue and West 34th Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
- [371] Man selling football paraphernalia, San Gennaro Festival, Grand Street, Little Italy, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
- [372] Superman float, San Gennaro Festival, Grand Street, Little Italy, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
- [373] Joe and the Juice cafe, Spring Street, Soho, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
- [374] John Jovino Gun Shop, Grand Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
- [375] Basketball player mural on building, Lafayette and Spring Streets, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
- [376] Pattern on wall, 8th Avenue at West 34th Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
- [377] Subway #7 Line stop at 11th Avenue, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
- [378] Einstein mural, West 14th Street near 12th Avenue, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
- [379] Kaleidoscope store front, Carmine Street, West Village, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
- [380] Subway station, Lexington Ave and 53rd St, looking up at Citicorp Building, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
- [381] Lady with stuffed pigeons, Union Square, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
- [382] Pattern on wall, West 34th St. and 8th Avenue, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
- [383] Mural, Desigual, 6th Ave. at East 35th St., 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
- [384] Poster, police brutality protest, West 185th St. and Audubon Ave., Washington Heights, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
- [385] Fallen police tribute wall, 9th Precinct, East 6th Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
- [386] Korilla Building, St. Mark's Place, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
- [387] Mural, West 155th St. and Broadway, Washington Heights, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
- [388] Maleta's Store, West 181st St. near Amsterdam Ave., Washington Heights, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
- [389] Space alien mannequin, West 39th St. near 8th Ave., 2016 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
- [390] Mural, Mulberry Street, Little Italy, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
- [391] Whitney Museum from the High Line, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
- [392] Poster tribute to fallen firefighters of 9/11, Vesey St., 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
- [393] Mural, upside down man, 10th Ave. at 18th St., Chelsea, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
- [394] Graffiti wall with baby picture, Houston St., 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
- [395] Brookfield Place lobby, West Side Highway, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
- [396] Jamaica Long Island Railroad Station, Queens, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
- [397] Jamaica Long Island Railroad Station #2, Queens, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
- [398] New World Trade Center subway entrance, Liberty Street, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
- [399] Wedding couple picture, East Broadway, Chinatown, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
- [400] David Bowie tribute wall, Lafayette St., Soho, 2016 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
- [401] PATH Train, Vesey St. entrance, 2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)